<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/tag/lore-tutoriais/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2019-01-25T08:31:14-02:00</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:4000/tag/lore-tutoriais/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">Forgotten Lore Shard | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Servidor Roleplay brasileiro de Ultima Online</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Aventure-se em Tybar</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aventure-se em Tybar" />
      <published>2017-07-27T07:00:00-03:00</published>
      <updated>2017-07-27T07:00:00-03:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/welcome</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome">Interpretação de personagens na terra dos seis povos

We know that first impressions are important, so we've populated your new site with some initial **Getting Started** posts that will help you get familiar with everything in no time. This is the first one!

### There are a few things that you should know up-front:
1. Ghost is designed for ambitious, professional publishers who want to actively build a business around their content. That's who it works best for. If you're using Ghost for some other purpose, that's fine too - but it might not be the best choice for you.
2. The entire platform can be modified and customized to suit your needs, which is very powerful, but doing so **does** require some knowledge of code. Ghost is not necessarily a good platform for beginners or people who just want a simple personal blog.
3. For the best experience we recommend downloading the Ghost Desktop App for your computer, which is the best way to access your Ghost site on a desktop device.


Ghost is made by an independent non-profit organisation called the Ghost Foundation. We are 100% self funded by revenue from our [Ghost(Pro)](https://ghost.org/pricing) service, and every penny we make is re-invested into funding further development of free, open source technology for modern journalism.

The main thing you'll want to read about next is probably: [the Ghost editor](https://demo.ghost.io/the-editor/).

Once you're done reading, you can simply delete the default **Ghost** user from your team to remove all of these introductory posts!</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Forgotten Lore Shard</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="lore tutoriais" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Interpretação de personagens na terra dos seis povos</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
